Sanjeev Suresh: Hey, Jordan.
Jordan Augé: Hey, how are you?
Sanjeev Suresh: I'm good.
Jordan Augé: Hi, David.
Jordan Augé: Hi, Nicola.
Nicolas Bonnet: Hello.
Jordan Augé: Right.
Jeffin Varghese: He goes.
Jordan Augé: So let's wait a traditional few minutes while we want to connect.
Jordan Augé: I will start showing the agenda.
Jordan Augé: Okay, we can quickly maybe review the agenda, so…
Jordan Augé: Basically, this is a bit like usual, so we'll start with general updates, then,
Jordan Augé: the deliverables we have in progress, taxonomy effort, and more importantly, the gap analysis.
Jordan Augé: And, I wanted to know first if you had something you would like to discuss or add.
Jordan Augé: Otherwise I can start with the update. So we had the
Jordan Augé: a long conversation with Kasper this week to try, to…
Jordan Augé: review the deliverables and raise ideas, so mostly a brainstorm.
Jordan Augé: So he shared the conversation, so don't hesitate to have a look. The summary is pretty accurate.
Jordan Augé: So we wanted to make a point on the summer PTO because we'll start to be away so fortunately Casper and myself so we put our dates of PTO so we are on PTO on different times so we should always have someone in the meeting so I guess it will continue over the summer and based on attendance we'll see what we can do.
Jordan Augé: Another update is that we did the first reporting to the technical committee, so this is a new process that's meant to be offline, so every month, the last day of the month, we are supposed to do a
Jordan Augé: a very succinct reporting of where we are, what are the next steps, blockers, etc. So, you can find the pull request. So, basically, that's a template we have to fill.
Jordan Augé: Then,
Jordan Augé: the technical committee is added as a reviewer, and they have a certain time to review it, and they approve or not the pull request. I think the… each working group has a kind of sponsor that will,
Jordan Augé: Try to give us advice, etc. I don't know yet who is exactly assigned to us.
Jordan Augé: No.
Jordan Augé: Two quick updates, so I didn't dedicate the time, but I added two entries in the table on the left.
Jordan Augé: So one is a 1st draft of the internal deliverable. That's the liaison with working group. So
Jordan Augé: This is mostly for you to have a look offline. I tried to…
Jordan Augé: List the different working groups in which we might have interactions with a few bullet points.
Jordan Augé: So…
Jordan Augé: basically what we expect as an input or an output to the different working groups. So I tried to look at the current state of deliverables and see what might be the interaction. So feel free to comment, add, remove stuff. So let's see.
Jordan Augé: if we can get rough ideas of the collaboration. And I guess we need to discuss soon with some of them, like, maybe observability,
Jordan Augé: So… Second point was about the
Jordan Augé: taxonomy. So if you remember last time we discussed, I made a pull request with a collection of words, so they were contributed to the general document, the cross working group document. So
Jordan Augé: I made just a page to track a bit the progress.
Jordan Augé: So the idea was to group those terms. We have a big number, actually, of words that are defined. So a lot of them, they are just common, like what is an agent model. So it's not a big deal. But I tried to classify the important ones according to three milestones, and I started to put them in the document.
Jordan Augé: So the idea is that Milestone 1 terms may be the terms we might want to really define first.
Jordan Augé: And for some of them, take ownership in the working group.
Jordan Augé: So, the idea is to look at the terms that were foundational, used in the deliverables, they were,
Jordan Augé: Defining the different sections, and try to make sure that we all take time to review them.
Jordan Augé: So, I tried to follow the…
Jordan Augé: Classification in Deliverable 1 to have categories of them.
Jordan Augé: And to put in bold the one that seems more important.
Jordan Augé: More important is maybe not,
Jordan Augé: Absolute. It's because maybe that's where we have the
Jordan Augé: the least contributions. Or maybe we had some contradictions in the literature. Or maybe we have a we had a discussion in the running notes.
Jordan Augé: Or maybe there are terms that I'm not sure we have an external definition, so…
Jordan Augé: The ones in bold would be the first one you should have a look if you wanted to give a review in M1.
Jordan Augé: So, of course, this is a suggestion. I welcome… we review this list also.
Jordan Augé: So again, don't hesitate to put comments on the list, the categories, what you think is priority.
Jordan Augé: And from there, you have a link at the beginning to the shared Google Doc.
Jordan Augé: So that's a kind of always evolving document. And the idea is that
Jordan Augé: I guess every 2 weeks they close a version, and we go through a cycle of iteration.
Jordan Augé: So, you will find all the words inside, so…
Jordan Augé: As an action point, I would encourage you to have a look, pick a few words, and try to see if you agree with the definition, etc, so that we have some kind of
Jordan Augé: Tracking, of the progress. And after, sometimes we can say, okay, this is,
Jordan Augé: the words we get assigned to the working group. These are the words that we think are well-defined, and
Jordan Augé: We can move, maybe, to the next milestone.
Jordan Augé: It would be nice to wrap the first one before,
Jordan Augé: mid-summer, somehow, before PTO, or after PTO.
Jordan Augé: Back to the notes.
Jordan Augé: Sorry I lost the running notes.
Jordan Augé: Okay, so…
Jordan Augé: For both, the idea is really to have a look offline and really comment and contribute. Don't hesitate to put questions, things that are not clear, or things you would like.
Jordan Augé: To be defined.
Jordan Augé: Next point is about, updates for the working group, so that was a suggestion last meeting, is just to open some time if someone had to share, anything.
Jordan Augé: A paper worth reading, an event worth attending, so…
Jordan Augé: Before we start to D3, if you have some things you want to share?
Sanjeev Suresh: I think if anyone is based out of the Bay Area, there is a MCP launch party, like AIF MCP launch party coinciding with the big MCP release on the 28th.
Jordan Augé: So maybe you can put just if you have a link to the.
Sanjeev Suresh: Yeah, I think the link for the event is still not yet out. When it's out, yeah, I can share in the discord.
Jordan Augé: Thank you.
Jordan Augé: So… Nothing else, maybe, Sanjeev, to you, if you want to…
Sanjeev Suresh: Yeah, let me share. Yes, I think some just quick updates from the last time. Let me share my screen.
Sanjeev Suresh: Okay.
Sanjeev Suresh: So some updates from last time, so we met once,
Sanjeev Suresh: last week around same time, and had a discussion on the gap analysis. We have a rough structure of the gap analysis, but as we were working through it, one of the things also we realized is this needs to be more grounded in real
Sanjeev Suresh: Enterprise issues.
Sanjeev Suresh: And, like, I think Jordan and Casper both, met once, like, after, the previous week's meeting, and also discussed more on that. And…
Sanjeev Suresh: like, one of the things we discussed was that we need some sort of, like, survey, and that might be useful to ground this work stream in.
Sanjeev Suresh: Jordan, do you want to add anything to that?
Jordan Augé: No, I think that was a very good idea from Casper. I don't know if he has joined yet.
Jordan Augé: Okay, I know he has some conflict during the time. So maybe it's not later. But he suggested that actually, that was from the discussion. We noticed that there are
Jordan Augé: some challenges that are more important, because not everyone is in a state where it will have a checklist of everything deployed to port. There are some, really, priorities. For some, it's the cost. For some, it's the usefulness.
Jordan Augé: For some, it's really security sandboxing, so…
Jordan Augé: we have the impression that people, they have a few top challenges they are solving, and they forget the rest. For example, most people, they are not deploying anything serving users, sometimes it's internal, so they don't need some,
Jordan Augé: some part of the reliability. We would like to focus, maybe.
Jordan Augé: more on the 1st use cases of importance, maybe of importance for the working group. So if we have people deploying application.
Jordan Augé: having some feedback on what you think is important. A few use cases we could use as the beginning of this deliverable that we could deploy, and maybe those use cases they could be. Let's say you have an autonomous open pro instance.
Jordan Augé: another one might be you have some Agentic system in CICD, another one, it's a very simple selling customers, and every situation.
Jordan Augé: You have different challenges, different priorities.
Jordan Augé: Maybe use some tools, open source or not, or product, so…
Jordan Augé: That could always be useful, not to promote this, but make a census of where people are.
Jordan Augé: So if it's open source, I mean, it fits well the IAF.
Jordan Augé: But we know what are the features we are using, and
Jordan Augé: with this we might see the gaps. Is some solution working with all frameworks? Are we able to operate the system? Do we have visibility? What do you measure? So all this kind of feedback, I guess, is really what we need to pursue this deliverable.
Sanjeev Suresh: Yeah, and like one of the things like, I mean, we had a really good discussion with the, I mean, few of us last week on like both the accuracy and reliability would be relative to some set of constraints and costs or something like that kept popping up across different use cases too, for example.
Sanjeev Suresh: One additional thing, so I was at a conference, the AI Engineers World's Fair last week, and I saw this Barry Yaron present on this 2026 AI engineering report. So they are by a group called Amplify. I think they partnered with Notion and one other.
Sanjeev Suresh: group to essentially do a survey on state of AI engineering. I just wanted to show this quickly.
Sanjeev Suresh: Because some of this might be, like, super relevant to our working group as well.
Sanjeev Suresh: This is, I think, they surveyed a group of 1,000 people, again, like founders, CTOs, AI engineers, like a very practitioner-focused crowd.
Sanjeev Suresh: And, I mean, first there's some demographic information, but I want to skip to…
Sanjeev Suresh: Yeah, so this is what are your three top considerations when choosing a model for production? Interestingly, the first one is accuracy slash quality.
Sanjeev Suresh: Cost is among the top three. One more interesting thing is reliability came after cost.
Sanjeev Suresh: Like, again, this is, I mean, just 1,000 people, but also, like, I mean, very practitioner-focused crowd, so cost is something really important.
Sanjeev Suresh: So something like, we might want to do, again, like a survey, and, and, and, and I'll post this link in the notes as well. This is, like, really interesting to take a look at this. Like, how do you decide what model to use? Do they route by cost, route by task?
Sanjeev Suresh: Do you want to stay flexible?
Sanjeev Suresh: Like, has cost ever made you dial back your AI ambitions? How do you give permissions? Is there a human in the loop?
Sanjeev Suresh: I think there was, like, some interesting one on, like, evals and monitoring, like, how do you monitor it?
Sanjeev Suresh: Yeah, so essentially, maybe as a first step for us to ground us in our use case,
Sanjeev Suresh: a survey like this would be useful. Like, again, like, I was just playing around with… and this is not ready in any shape, but, like, again, I was playing around with a proposed survey for, like, grounding in our use case. Again.
Sanjeev Suresh: We may want, like, again, something like 15 questions or 15 to 20 questions at most.
Sanjeev Suresh: A few demographic information about, like, who you are.
Sanjeev Suresh: maybe we want some sort of section on, like, what is the agent system that you are building, right? Because we want to understand use cases more. Is it, like, a single model thing, multiple model thing?
Sanjeev Suresh: Like, what are the biggest obstacles you're facing when, when, you want to put your agent to production?
Sanjeev Suresh: And again, ground in things that we are seeing as potential options.
Sanjeev Suresh: Like, what additional time, is spent, developing new features versus, like, testing and building reliability.
Sanjeev Suresh: An interesting question might be on, like, failure modes, like, what are incidents that's caused in production based on agents that you put up?
Sanjeev Suresh: Sections on, like, more on, like, failures.
Sanjeev Suresh: I'll just skip, like, and maybe, like, some part on, like, how do you, like, measure and eval agents in production?
Sanjeev Suresh: I can put… I can also copy-paste this as, again, a starting point of conversation.
Sanjeev Suresh: This…
Sanjeev Suresh: we'll definitely need to crowdsource questions as well, but, I mean, something like this would be the idea for the survey, and we'll end, like, end with, I mean, some sort of, like, free form.
Sanjeev Suresh: Text as well.
Sanjeev Suresh: I'll stop here for thoughts and questions.
Sanjeev Suresh: Nicholas.
Nicolas Bonnet: Sanjeev, quick question. I really think this is a good idea to have a survey. Do you think it should be applied to just our working group or could it be applied across the working groups to expand a little bit the reach
Nicolas Bonnet: and because I assume it would be interesting to to look above like across the working groups.
Sanjeev Suresh: Like, I would think also probably across is useful, like, and many of our questions are even, like, across as well, like, Jordan, what do you think?
Jordan Augé: Yeah, I think we need to…
Jordan Augé: maybe sync a bit with our working groups. But and and maybe the
Jordan Augé: the TC, but I think this is a good idea to do it cross AAF. So, last time I scheduled this meeting, and I noticed, by mistake, I pinged the 150 persons, which are in the working group, so…
Jordan Augé: If we extend, that means we have a solid base, and if the report is not too bad, we could say, okay, this is based on the outcome that we might commit to work on certain aspects first, so…
Jordan Augé: People can have an overview of.
Jordan Augé: The field, what others are doing, which is non-concurrential, of course, and maybe they can benefit from the work we do, so…
Jordan Augé: I think it's a great ideas.
Nicolas Bonnet: Yeah. And I and I think that to see Well.
Nicolas Bonnet: demographics. But I assume, like our roles like to see the distribution of roles and and
Nicolas Bonnet: what other functions are being represented across the working groups would be quite interesting, I think.
Sanjeev Suresh: And I don't know whether we want to limit, and just like an open discussion, like, do we want to limit to just working groups? Like, I mean, the survey can be broadly shared as well, right?
Nicolas Bonnet: Kim.
Jordan Augé: The only challenge, I guess, is having not too many questions, so that people, they will spend the time to do it. So that's the biggest challenge, I guess.
Jordan Augé: And clearly explain how the data will be used, so those are the two things.
Jordan Augé: But I guess…
Sanjeev Suresh: Exact.
Jordan Augé: There's a way for people to make a one-shot contribution that will, be quite impactful, so…
Sanjeev Suresh: Yeah, and we can probably promote in some sort of, like, the newsletter or something, so that, like, it reaches more people to… My only one concern with just the cross…
Sanjeev Suresh: Working group thing is, like, how long would it take to, like, reach consensus to get the final survey to be sent out?
Sanjeev Suresh: Just to, like… Keep the momentum going on this work stream.
Jordan Augé: So I guess we need a period of time where we work on it. From there, the recommendation from…
Jordan Augé: AIF was really to…
Jordan Augé: communicate about it. Maybe we can send an email to the working group for that, so that people have time to review.
Sanjeev Suresh: Mmm.
Jordan Augé: After some time, whoever has contributed, we can take into account, and…
Jordan Augé: then we can make a vote in the meeting and and proceed. So we should not try to reach everyone's consensus. It's mostly
Jordan Augé: on participation and consensus during meeting from active people. So that's what they recommended us. Otherwise we never progress.
Sanjeev Suresh: Yeah, makes sense.
Jordan Augé: No, it's really nice for you from contributing to the start, so…
Jordan Augé: So, action point also is to look at questions and Put comments.
Sanjeev Suresh: Any other thoughts from folks, especially folks who, have, I mean, talk, who we have been talking last time, Jesse, Matt, Matthew, I see Brian.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: Okay.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: I'm gonna be very selfish here.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: But I just spent 15 minutes fighting with my laptop to… and it ended up me needing to reboot Linux.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: And I'm still trying to gain my bearings here.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: So, please give me a couple minutes so that I can, get all the curses out of my system.
Jessie Zhang: So, I'm still a little bit confused about the responsibility, because every conversation we have, we…
Jessie Zhang: kind of extend a little bit, and kind of went to a little bit different direction. So, maybe we can talk about, at least have the first version, that the deadline, who's doing what, and what we should cover, so we look at that again.
Jordan Augé: So, no, I would just comment that this survey is not a change of direction, it was more trying to have an answer on,
Jordan Augé: The lack of, maybe, grounding to… What is really needed, because…
Jordan Augé: a risk that was surfaced by the Tc. When we did the charter was that we keep being theoretical, and we try to boil the ocean, and we don't make a practical answer to practitioners like a short term impact.
Jordan Augé: and we noticed that the sections that are still missing in the deliverables are the 1st one where you try to define use cases, etc. So that was an attempt.
Jordan Augé: at collecting information to populate those sections. So it's not really, I think, different directions. It was just a suggestion to solve
Jordan Augé: This problem.
Jessie Zhang: So I'm not talking about… actually, I want to kind of make it clear. I'm not saying about the survey. I feel like every conversation, we… last time, talking about cost, before talking about model, talking about different things.
Jessie Zhang: Maybe survey is the right way to go. But I just feel like this gap analysis.
Jessie Zhang: Sanjeev, between your first time having that, it's been many weeks, right? So what is, do we have deadline, or it's just…
Jessie Zhang: Oh, we can just discuss and continue.
Jessie Zhang: Looking at it. So we need to have at this, like, one first version, right? And then we will look at it again, saying, hey, we gotta go look at different things.
Jessie Zhang: I just feel a little bit. I'll say I'm a little bit lost. I kind of not sure how we can, how I can contribute anymore.
Sanjeev Suresh: I mean, I'll give my take and I'll let Jordan chime in as well. I mean, for me, like, I think, like, again, like, I don't know whether actually we have any hard and fast deadlines.
Sanjeev Suresh: And.
Sanjeev Suresh: I mean, the value is in, to me, like, like, I want to make sure, like, whatever we produce is useful.
Sanjeev Suresh: And I don't know whether we have that right framing yet in that grounding. And I feel you, Jesse, on that. We seem to be still trying to figure out what going in different directions and trying to figure out whether we should go broader, narrower.
Sanjeev Suresh: Yeah, and I don't know whether we have defined that yet. Like, even…
Sanjeev Suresh: Just over the last two weeks, the taxonomy itself changed quite a bit, right?
Sanjeev Suresh: So… And that's the ground beneath even the gap analysis.
Jordan Augé: Yes, so just to answer on deadlines, so I think we have no urgency for this D3. So the initial idea was really, so what is important is contribute to the taxonomy effort because that's where there is active work and
Jordan Augé: to make it feasible when you have not a lot of time. That's why we try to propose this milestones.
Jordan Augé: And Matthew, we can come back to that just after.
Jordan Augé: In terms of D3, the idea was to have, advanced… Dude.
Jordan Augé: the table of content and the content of deliverable before summer, so that it can be continued after. I think we are,
Jordan Augé: There yet, thanks to this effort.
Jordan Augé: My fear is that, many people who had,
Jordan Augé: content to contribute did it, and so I fear that we still lack
Jordan Augé: use cases, etc. And this is information that is quite hard to obtain. So that's why we are searching for alternatives.
Jordan Augé: And,
Jordan Augé: I don't think we have enough voices yet in the content of the deliverable we produce, so… not enough comments, etc. So, I think that's the priority.
Jordan Augé: Even if you think that you don't have much time, etc, just commenting on rough ID would be great.
Sanjeev Suresh: Yeah, yeah.
Sanjeev Suresh: That's, yeah, go ahead.
Vellaichamy, Sivapriya: Yeah, I was thinking, is it… I know we don't have an immediate deadline. Would it be okay if we have some kind of a deadline for first draft?
Vellaichamy, Sivapriya: come with… To.
Jordan Augé: So before deadlines, I would say we need the people that commit.
Vellaichamy, Sivapriya: 3… 2… 1…
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: Is SIVA breaking up for everyone else?
Sanjeev Suresh: Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, breaking up.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: I feel less bad.
Sanjeev Suresh: I mean, so I think, I mean, like, I think the question was on, could we have some deadlines, like, honestly, I think maybe we can probably have a better deadline on a survey, because I think that seems more concrete.
Sanjeev Suresh: And gap analysis, I don't know whether.
Sanjeev Suresh: We are there yet in which we even have a what is the scope of what we are doing.
Jordan Augé: Yeah, I guess before setting deadlines on deliverable, we need to know what the working group wants to do.
Jordan Augé: And, really, the work will be what we decide is the work, so…
Jordan Augé: If we have enough people interested in topics that will cover the deliverable, then we can assign maybe,
Jordan Augé: one lead to each section, and then we can start to commit, but for now, I don't think we have enough,
Jordan Augé: Engagement across the working group to set deadlines.
Jordan Augé: Yep, so… Mathieu or Nicolas, I don't know who started first.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: I'm going to say Nicolas.
Nicolas Bonnet: I did? All right. I wanted to maybe try to help with this discussion and try to…
Nicolas Bonnet: go deeper in this discussion about use cases.
Nicolas Bonnet: Because I think for me, it's extremely difficult to have really
Nicolas Bonnet: quality output of our work. If it's not rooted in a use case, and and I can't talk about accuracy and reliability.
Nicolas Bonnet: independently of the use case. It's all relative to the use case. If the use case is to educate myself of this agent is to educate myself on something.
Nicolas Bonnet: I.
Nicolas Bonnet: the… how I'm gonna measure accuracy and reliability is very different in that if the use case is to execute a task on my behalf, right? So I think there… for us, like, you know, Jesse and I at Autodesk have created a…
Nicolas Bonnet: taxonomy of use cases, which is, it's fairly simple. It's like, help me. It covers like, help me educate me versus do it for me. And I think
Nicolas Bonnet: without that framing, I don't think this, you know, we can talk about accuracy. It is so related to this. So I think it would be really helpful, maybe in the survey, to use that kind of framework.
Nicolas Bonnet: to say what is the nature of the use cases that you guys are working on? Because I really think that you can only talk about accuracy in the context of
Nicolas Bonnet: Of the.
Nicolas Bonnet: output of the work that the user is trying to do, and the level of trustworthiness depends on the level of risk associated with an agent doing something on your behalf.
Nicolas Bonnet: So I really think there's a framework that is missing here that would really help, you know, be more precise about that discussion. If not, it's too high level for me to intervene, actually.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: I would like, could you please expand on how accuracy and risk are correlated?
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: Maybe I misunderstood.
Nicolas Bonnet: So…
Nicolas Bonnet: to, like, you know, in our context, I'm going to talk a little bit about specific, about how we.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: Yeah, sure.
Nicolas Bonnet: Sure. Different workflows have different risk profiles. When an engineer wants to design a bridge and think of…
Nicolas Bonnet: the load, you know, what is the load that this bridge is going to take? It has an enormous risk associated with the risk profile of the workflow is very high.
Nicolas Bonnet: When an engineer wants to understand a feature of one of our products and what are the capabilities, it's a low risk. It's kind of learning things. So we try to categorize that, you know, to…
Nicolas Bonnet: inspect the answers of the agent in light of the risk profile of the workflow. If it's informational versus really do it for me, I want to trust you to do this task for me, and it's a high-risk task, then we apply much more granular inspection.
Nicolas Bonnet: So, I think for me, like, to really… it would… it would…
Nicolas Bonnet: try to divvy up the kind of use cases by their by their outcomes would really help ground the discussion.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: So I get that.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: I feel then that risk, It has a dependency of accuracy, but accuracy doesn't have a dependency of risk.
Nicolas Bonnet: Yes, it's the the Yeah, you're right. I think it is accurate or not accurate.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: Okay.
Nicolas Bonnet: And what you're going to do with this depends on the level of risk associated with, you're right, correct.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: Absolutely, and here's my big red flag from what you said, and this is actually.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: I'm sorry, this needs to be escalated to AIF.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: There's nothing about safety in here, in the working groups.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: We're the closest match to safety here, this is bad.
Nicolas Bonnet: Can you explain more? Can you explain what you mean by this word?
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: Okay, so this working group, Accuracy and reliability.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: Are the closest thing to safety.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: But I can see… Okay, you're saying that agent reliability is… Connected to safety? I'm…
Sanjeev Suresh: I mean, so I think… I think that's tenuous.
Sanjeev Suresh: Yeah, like safety is mentioned along with reliability, asset reliability dimension, but also at least my understanding of this terminology, like we want to also talk about it separately too.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: Yes.
Sanjeev Suresh: And I think that Princeton reliability HAL leaderboard, they also have a single reliability score, but also report safety like.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: Okay.
Sanjeev Suresh: Like, as an adjacent access.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: And.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: I'm… I'm sure that Nicholas… And Jesse will agree that safety is a giant can of monkeys, also.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: Like, I don't want to put more on Jordan and Casper's shoulders.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: But this is a… Big old debate.
Sanjeev Suresh: Yeah, I think, I mean, to me also, like, I mean, the biggest things, I mean, safety and cost is probably the biggest concerns I've heard.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: Yes.
Sanjeev Suresh: Very anecdotally.
Jordan Augé: Yeah, I I guess this, I mean, can interpret it in many ways. So that that's why this there is discussion about qualifying better the term safety, because we might think it's more security. We might think it's many things still. I think all the subject of the
Jordan Augé: silent issues, hallucinations are directly related to harmful actions. You might call a tool which is not
Jordan Augé: which is not meant to. And all the concept of sandboxes, etc, they are reliability actions that you are doing in your system to
Jordan Augé: self-corrected by cutting the evolutions that are bad, so…
Jordan Augé: I think it's in this sense I was seeing it.
Jordan Augé: Then this terminology, I guess it's my 1st shot, and we had no consensus, nothing. So it's really a 1st contribution.
Jordan Augé: It was meant as a base for discussion, but I don't think it represents any consensus or whatever.
Sanjeev Suresh: So Jeff, I'll just come to you. So I need to drop in like a couple of minutes. So just as next steps.
Sanjeev Suresh: like, one thing I would just encourage everyone to do is actually take part in discussions offline. Again, some details of
Sanjeev Suresh: Terminology, it's hard to flesh out in a live discussion forum here, where people might also need to, like, think
Sanjeev Suresh: so I would encourage, like, everyone to, like, participate in the Discord, and also just, like, again, to set another time for, like, a possible discussion.
Sanjeev Suresh: Probably again, like, sometime next week, say, next Tuesday, around this time, and we can, discuss in Discord as well.
Jessie Zhang: We also do something ahead of time, like a survey, right? Just use AI to based on, 'cause you have that doc, that paper, or based on what we have, then generate a bunch of things.
Jessie Zhang: I'm sorry.
Sanjeev Suresh: Yeah, let's chat like, I mean, like actually in Discord on that, right? So, I mean, so that our Slack.
Jessie Zhang: Yeah, otherwise, we go into this meeting, we're only gonna talk, right? If we're gonna do… so I'm looking for, like, some work, like, ahead of time, just do it, and then go there, just discuss it. So, homework.
Jessie Zhang: Umm.
Jessie Zhang: So if I don't, if I understand right, the priority is the taxonomy first, right?
Jessie Zhang: In this survey, Then, maybe look at the, coverage of, analysis, gap analysis.
Jordan Augé: And maybe Jesse, I know you were interested really in a lot of the user facing accuracy reliability. So if you have a contribution to make there, I guess it could be very interesting because it's a use case that interests you. And that's one dimension of evaluation of the system. So if you have comments on that part, that could be also interesting.
Jessie Zhang: Not good.
Jordan Augé: So maybe Siva Priya? Yes. Before we continue?
Jordan Augé: Are you back, somehow?
Sanjeev Suresh: And I know Jeff…
Vellaichamy, Sivapriya: Yeah. Hi, Jordan. Yeah.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: You sound much better.
Jordan Augé: Yes.
Vellaichamy, Sivapriya: Okay.
Vellaichamy, Sivapriya: So, you know, this covered it. I just wanted to know the priority on things that we can start contributing. So, yeah, this was good. I've been able to hear all this discussion, so that's good.
Vellaichamy, Sivapriya: Yeah, thank you.
Sanjeev Suresh: And Jeff, you had a hand raised earlier too, Jeff Borek.
Jeff Borek: Thanks. In addition to the 2 major
Jeff Borek: concerns. I was going to add a 3rd
Jeff Borek: Which is not an easy one, but.
Jeff Borek: The idea of value.
Jeff Borek: Because… I think we're at a inflection point where Increasingly.
Jeff Borek: In addition to concerns over the security, accuracy, and reliability.
Jeff Borek: how can… you in a Some sort of a not too complicated way.
Jeff Borek: prove, you know, Value.
Jeff Borek: But that may not be a specific focus of this particular working group. Thanks.
Jordan Augé: Okay, so Sandrine, thanks for the work.
Jordan Augé: No, my… Comment on that would be,
Jordan Augé: That we need, really, to try working more offline. Really, don't hesitate to put just a single comment, and that might give rise to discussion.
Jordan Augé: If you have a section of interest to you, really the idea is to self-assign you, start contributing comments, and
Jordan Augé: we can see, how it comes. And the idea of this meeting, so I think it's fine to explore things, but at some point, we really need to work offline, provide content, and use the live meeting for,
Jordan Augé: Feedback on what was done, and presenting the results, etc, so…
Jordan Augé: we need really to try to organize better the offline, I guess.
Jordan Augé: Yep, so, Mathieu, you wanted to say something still?
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: Yes, I'm… I was actually hoping that Claude would answer me before, I could ask the question. I wanted to suggest that we have two surveys.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: One that's lightweight, 5 randomized questions from the bucket that we put everywhere.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: And I mean, not just AEIF, on your Twitters, on your internal polls, everywhere.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: And that would be for consultation data.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: So it's not long, gets people just, thanks, thank you, you did it.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: And then we have the full-fat one that we keep internally.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: I… and I was hoping that Claude would be able to show me some infrastructure that could allow us to do it for free, because I like contributing actual solutions, not just suggestions.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: But, yeah.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: I wanted to have a smell check on that idea.
Jordan Augé: Yeah, so maybe an action point for the chairs would be to see if IAF is fine also with this way of…
Jordan Augé: Reaching out a bit externally, and even internally.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: It would be for consultation purposes,
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: How would they… how would they object to this?
Jordan Augé: I just to to to inform them.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: I know. I'm… I'm just suggesting that this is one of those ask-for-forgiveness situations.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: And if they want to be careful, they just should step up and attend these meetings with us.
Jordan Augé: That's a good way to see
Jordan Augé: Okay, so even in the working group, so if you can share on Discord, what is… if you had… I mean, you joined this working group because I guess you had some intent in mind, so I would like to know better
Jordan Augé: What would be the ideal outcome that you would get first from accuracy, reliability? What is something that will solve the problem that you have today?
Jordan Augé: So it's fine if you are just there for just seeing what happens, but if you came with a problem.
Jordan Augé: Really share it, don't hesitate
Jordan Augé: Not wait for the survey.
Jordan Augé: Okay, so I guess we can wrap up on D3, and since Sanjeev is not there, we try to continue that offline in Discord.
Jordan Augé: So the last point in the agenda was an update. Wait, take 10 min.
Jordan Augé: So update on taxonomy effort and the one. So I guess we covered it quite well. So
Jordan Augé: So just as a recap, so… We have this.
Jordan Augé: Internet document. I don't know, Matthew, if you saw that. So I just recap in the
Jordan Augé: In the document, in the running notes, the milestone and the terms, so that if people want to contribute, they can just go to the…
Jordan Augé: Google Docs, so I've seen you share an Excel sheet, so maybe.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: I think this is something that I'm going to try to share it and we'll see if it goes horribly wrong or not.
Jordan Augé: The idea was to point people to Milestone 1 definitions, so the more that maybe are more important, so that people can contribute, if they agree with.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: Yes.
Jordan Augé: and to look at those words in the taxonomy.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: So here's one thing that I have as an ask for the team.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: I made a best honest effort.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: For accuracy and reliability, cull the list from For from 100 something to.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: Like… 30 items, or 25 items.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: And I also… Took the liberty of taking some items.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: And suggesting they get merged into other people's, lists so that we have less of a burden on everyone.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: I would like everyone to take a look and say, hey, Matthew, you not smart person.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: You got rid of my favorite word.
Jordan Augé: So what we need is really to share this. So is the sheet replicating the Google Docs that we have?
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: The sheet is not repeating, it's summarizing and putting it in a…
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: And then putting it with all the other stuff. So you have observability, you have workflows, security and privacy, governance, risk and regulatory, identity and trust.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: and universal. And the universal one's the important one. Once we start getting the ones that are… that trickle up, because it's, let's say, in accuracy, observability, and security.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: Goes to the top.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: And these are the things that we agree on, and that When I say, for example.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: Accuracy, I don't mean cost.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: It's the definitions that are universally agreed on, and then these… the other ones are the specific
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: Working group maintained ones.
Jordan Augé: But we had, I sent it in chat, we had a Google Doc shared last time that is cross-working group also.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: Yes. Oh, that's old.
Jordan Augé: No, that's all okay.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: Yes.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: So they tried doing that, and it got very big and hard to search, so we made it into this Google Doc Sheets thing.
Jordan Augé: Okay, so I need to share this new sheet in the meeting.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: Yes.
Jordan Augé: Okay, so that's the updated action point. Really take those priority items, take the cursor liability, and I'll make this one in the meeting, because that's how the ones that we want to address.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: And I, I basically took your definitions and had my handy-dandy agent condense them into one-liners.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: Which is why there's so many em dashes, but I've decided to keep it, we're in an AI group, it would be dishonest
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: Please… Check if there's anything that you… disagree with.
Brian Malone: Matthew, could I ask a question on this? Maybe two.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: As many as you, well, as many as everyone else has patience for.
Brian Malone: Well, so first, did you go, did you, take all the documents that we have for accuracy and reliability and run it through some sort of LLM and say, what are all the keywords that we should be looking at?
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: No, that's not a bad idea. What I did was I took the definitions. We had 156 definitions.
Brian Malone: Yes.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: And I just…
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: took all of that document, and I summarized all the definitions, made it into an Excel sheet.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: And then during the taxonomy working group meeting, I pasted it in there.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: And watched everyone's face go pale.
Brian Malone: Well, so, this will bring… might bring me to my second question, which is maintenance. So… Yes.
Brian Malone: One, like it seems to me, and I'll see if I can simplify this down of what I kind of have in my mind, which is to say we have 261 different keywords being defined right now, and those are being redefined literally daily, if not hourly at this point, right? So I'm just kind of wondering, like, do we establish, like we say, here are all the documents that are across all the different working groups.
Brian Malone: Here are some of the ones that overlap. Those will become universal. There are other ones become specific working group ones. And then every week we have a new PR of here are all the changes to definitions. And somebody or an agent could go through and say, yes, this is a meaningful difference from what we had before, or this is a version, you know, 2.0, whatever, right?
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: So that's, okay, this Excel sheet is an intermediate step.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: This is basically a triage ground before we make PRs with markdown files that go into that big website thing.
Brian Malone: Okay.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: So all of your CI, Should be on that side.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: And I want to be very clear and on the record. I absolutely love that idea.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: But this is this is really.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: I think I'm one of the nerdier people in that room.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: And so people… so basically, we reduced it to Excel because Markdown is a little… intense for some.
Brian Malone: Totally, yeah, but it's just not very agent-friendly at times, so…
Brian Malone: Yeah, so I'm just kind of like, again, I'm trying to think about this from, like, even just 3 months from now. Like, it's… at 262, it's already becoming beastly, and…
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: Yes.
Brian Malone: Again, you and I are in a bunch of working groups together. We know how much this stuff gets discussed.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: Absolutely, there's
Brian Malone: Waterf.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: By the way, these guys are…
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: There are many that are cropped already, so it's 114 just It's still locked.
Brian Malone: Oh, yeah, right. Sorry. So yeah, I just like a plan for how taxonomy gets managed is probably worthwhile before we go too far human in the loop, which we.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: Absolutely. So I have a question, and this is not trying to put you on the spot. I'd love you to be in the taxonomy group too. You have the time.
Brian Malone: Yeah, okay.
Brian Malone: I, no. Okay. No.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: Okay, and secondary offer, if you want me to be a soccer puppet for any of your ideas, don't hesit.
Brian Malone: Well, I mean, I think you already have good ideas and you're implementing them, which is great, and you're doing way more work than I could in the same period of time, but like, it just seems like this is a collection of effort that would be hard to maintain after people lose their passion for it.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: I get it. I 100% get it. We need to make sure that it's maintainable. That's why it's being converted to markdown into a static HTML and maintained by Junji at Google.
Brian Malone: Yep.
Brian Malone: Yeah, yeah.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: But, you know, this is not something…
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: This is something that's gonna be living.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: We're just doing all these extra steps right now because of the big bang.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: we're kind of expecting that it's going to be a huge expansion, and then that the inertia… that the energy kind of slows down. It's just like APIs.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: I've rarely seen an API evolve past version 40.
Brian Malone: Yeah, but, like, if you think about a dictionary and the iterations of words over, like, literally hundreds of years, like.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: Yes.
Brian Malone: All of them were correct at one point in time, and we… we sort of, like, dig into the details when we're gonna go.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: Yeah.
Brian Malone: Different levels of things, when it would probably be better to say, here's the provenance for the original definition of this, and then we can immediately access via an agent if we need to have access to it, if so being. Anyways, you've heard my concerns, and Jesse should have the floor because he probably has better ideas on this too.
Jordan Augé: Did you see?
Jessie Zhang: So is this a document, this a spreadsheet?
Jessie Zhang: This thing, just the big bucket.
Jessie Zhang: Of the accuracy and reliability, or every, what we call… It's everything.
Jessie Zhang: Because it's a very high level, right? Because if you look at your backup infrastructure.
Jessie Zhang: those things. So this is just a huge bucket. Then we're gonna each bucket. We define more taxonomy. Okay.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: I should mention also, if you look here, it's everyone's…
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: review. So if you want to add a review, just add a column with your name and put your opinions away right here.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: We have columns P through Y that are available.
Jessie Zhang: Okay, yeah, because I say correctness, the quality. So that is, let's say it's not there, right? Quality is not just.
Jessie Zhang: It being correct, being also helpful.
Jessie Zhang: Useful. So I don't see something. Okay. So we can just add a separate column adding things in there.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: Yes. So if you have something that you want to add, you put it on a row.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: And if you have opinions, you put in the column.
Jessie Zhang: Okay.
Jessie Zhang: Thanks.
Jordan Augé: And maybe just one more.
Jordan Augé: Brian. So the initial list. Actually, this is something I made using AI.
Jordan Augé: So I tried to collect the information that we had in the different deliverables, the running notes, the discussion that we had, the papers also that were in the notes to have this big list. That's why it's huge. There are a lot of terms that are model and agent, very common. So the real list is not that huge. There are many terms with a consensus. So.
Jordan Augé: I think it's good for completeness, they will move to the general section. The ones that we need to define is still big, but it's quite hierarchical, so the proposal was to start with big categories.
Jordan Augé: Like, what is accuracy, reliability, what are the four dimensions in accuracy, and dig more and more. And for correctness, it's the same. I guess it's a very vague term, but it's a dimension of evaluation, and then we can,
Jordan Augé: dig down and clearly say this is a rough word. Usually it's understood in this direction.
Jordan Augé: But… Qualify it if you want to be really technical.
Jordan Augé: Like, hallucination. Avoid it in technical documents, it might be good in the…
Jordan Augé: communication side. So we can have this kind of definitions.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: I just want to give context on a…
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: You know, the AAIF did not define Agentic yet.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: Okay.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: So, I just want us to be clear on where we're starting from.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: I think we've defined AI, but that's it. And foundation.
Jordan Augé: So the only restriction we know is that we don't want to cover models in this working group.
Jordan Augé: But then, whether it's agents, multi-agent systems.
Jordan Augé: Or even, I don't know how it could be called, I've seen workflow, I've seen other things, so this is a very ambiguous term, the system with agents and everything around, like durable execution system, like databases, memories, etc.
Jordan Augé: How do you call this big system? I don't know. But those are the different boundaries we might want to look at.
Jordan Augé: Just not go to the model.
Jordan Augé: But again, we need, different views and, sometimes it's such a…
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: They define model right here.
Jordan Augé: Yeah, I think we need a definition of model. We just don't want to make accuracy and reliability evaluations on models. I think that's out of scope.
Jordan Augé: But agent, I think it's a good example. When we started working internally on agents, we spent the years defining agents, and everyone had a different vision, so…
Jordan Augé: Yeah, the one world we could define.
Jordan Augé: That would be nice.
Jordan Augé: Okay, so no, really, big action point. It would be nice if everyone tried to spend,
Jordan Augé: Tonight, just look at the document, pick one word, put a comment, just that would be,
Jordan Augé: Helpful for your domain, what matters to you?
Jordan Augé: And I would encourage also, when you agree, put like a thumbs up somewhere, so that we know that we had the consensus on something.
Jordan Augé: Because, silence, we don't know if it's no one look at it, or everyone agrees, so…
Jordan Augé: That's it.
Jordan Augé: Anyone else you wanted to share, Matthew?
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: No, that's it. I wanted to mention also that if you're feeling mean, you can also do that. I mean, like.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: Saying remove this from the, from the taxonomy, no one cares about this word is.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: Perfectly valid, because it allows us to prioritize other words.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: But of course, we're all professionals, we'll say it in a much better way than what.
Jordan Augé: And maybe don't remove what is in the working group title, but then all the rest is…
Jordan Augé: I think accuracy, reliability, I think it's fine to define it. It's a very big term that encompasses, like,
Jordan Augé: Things related to one execution, and things related to the…
Jordan Augé: multiple evolution, which is the the definition in Princeton, and maybe that's sufficient and say, Okay, focus more than on the dimensions of accuracy.
Jordan Augé: So that people know what is the working group about, and then we can…
Jordan Augé: Continue. We need to spend years on these high-level, vague words.
Jordan Augé: Okay, and we have at the top of the hour, so we have 4 minutes left if you want to share last things. Anyone?
Jessie Zhang: Just want to make sure. Oh, go ahead.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: Please.
Jessie Zhang: Okay, just want to make sure when we talk about service. So so I put the to do on this already, right? That excel. I definitely have my opinion. I'm just I always
Jessie Zhang: have opinions, so I'll update that. So for the survey, what is the goal? What is the outcome do we want to achieve? Is that looking for use cases?
Jessie Zhang: Oh.
Jessie Zhang: Did we document anything on it?
Jordan Augé: So I don't think there is much document yet. It was just an idea from class pair last week that we try to have for solving this problem that we have no content in the.
Jordan Augé: Use case.
Jordan Augé: The idea is really, we want to know what are the top priority we need to tackle, what is the…
Jordan Augé: The first thing we could produce that is immediately usable for someone interested in the working group, so…
Jordan Augé: Not much than that. Being really pragmatic and deliver a solution. Low-hanging fruit, somehow.
Jessie Zhang: Okay.
Jessie Zhang: So there's a survey basically just trying to figure out the priority, not trying to figure out the use cases and to help us on the gap analysis, right?
Jordan Augé: It's not clear. I mean, it…
Jessie Zhang: Go.
Jordan Augé: It needs to be what the working group wants it to be. I don't think we have any preconceived idea.
Jordan Augé: Just, individual suggestions, and… If we're enough sharing consensus, let's do it.
Jordan Augé: And I think that's the role of this working group, is we can express all opinions, and we will work on where there is consensus and no concurrency, and
Jordan Augé: Where we disagree, let's leave it apart. It's something we want
Jordan Augé: Do in a working group, maybe.
Jessie Zhang: Okay. Yeah, because definitely,
Jessie Zhang: Great. That's a priority. Then we can do a priority later on. We can do the use case and taxonomy, even in terms of taxonomy, right? Even Nicola and I, we disagree on a bunch of definitions.
Jessie Zhang: We didn't order. That's where 2 leads we disagree like a quality. What does quality means? Right? What does trustworthiness means? So
Jessie Zhang: Yeah.
Jessie Zhang: So that that is my, actually my absolute top priority. Define what those things.
Jessie Zhang: I mean, for us, or agree on something.
Jessie Zhang: So we can move forward.
Jordan Augé: I think if the outcome is that the term quality is vague, and maybe has different meanings across individuals, or across different communities, or developers and product managers, they don't seem the same, I think it's a good outcome, and that means we need to qualify further what are the dimensions.
Jordan Augé: Oh, hopefully I'm just…
Jordan Augé: understood. And from there, that's already a contribution. We don't need to have an agreement. Already listing the disagreement is good.
Jordan Augé: Outcome.
Jessie Zhang: Yeah, 'cause I already disagree on the dementia. I had my opinions, did not disagree. Add my opinions on there, right? So, okay, sounds good. Thanks.
Jordan Augé: And maybe we can see what other people think of opinions, and maybe there is one that is doing consensus, and so…
Jordan Augé: I think that's… Raising everyone's opinion, I think, is a good contribution.
Jordan Augé: Matthew, you wanted to say something?
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: Well, we have one minute left, but I was going to ask if there are any cool developments in all the AIF projects that we should know about in accuracy and reliability.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: like, MCP has attestations coming in, maybe, and that's gonna be really cool for security, but I don't see much in accuracy yet
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: And I'd like to see this as a recurring
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: Near the end, hey, what's the world doing so that we're not just staying separate from the world.
Jordan Augé: Yeah, it's my bad, because I put it into the introduction section, but I did not…
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: Didn'.
Jordan Augé: Well, as what is the world doing? So do we have a.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: We have a recording? Okay, we'll check it because I,
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: I was fighting with Zoom this… at the beginning of the meeting. Sorry.
Jordan Augé: No, no, it's fine, but do we have in the group people contributing to MCP, GOOS, etc.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: I'm trying.
Jordan Augé: Active participants, I mean, among us.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: Yes, I'm trying to contribute to MCP.
Jordan Augé: Okay.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: And honestly, I'm trying to get Goose to set up good first issues so that I can bring interns in on that.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: But I'm trying on the social side a little more than the code side on Goose.
Jordan Augé: And again, it's fine. I think it's if you can share things you are doing blog posts that are related to accuracy.
Jordan Augé: Please do it.
Jeff Borek: Are you getting good receptivity?
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: Ahhh.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: They're very busy individuals, and I… they don't know who the heck I am yet, so…
Jordan Augé: Yet.
Jeff Borek: Understood.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: That's I realize that I have a very stinky name, and that I'll spread.
Jordan Augé: Okay, I think it's a great final word for the meeting.
Jordan Augé: Let's keep it up here.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: Okay.
Jordan Augé: Thank you. Everyone. So.
Jordan Augé: That's the.
Accurately Mtaahew Khouzam: To all those in security, I'll see you in security.
Jordan Augé: Thank you.
Jessie Zhang: Goodbye.
Jordan Augé: Have a nice week.